[{"id":733,"question":"How to watch rolling update status of \"frontend\" deployment until completion in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl rollout status --live deployment\/frontend","answer_b":"kubectl rollout status -w deployment\/frontend","answer_c":"kubectl rollout status -l deployment\/frontend","answer_d":"kubectl rollout status -s deployment\/frontend","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":692,"question":"Which service runs on each Kubernetes node and ensures containers are running in a pod?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"etcd","answer_b":"kubelet","answer_c":"scheduler","answer_d":"kubeadm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kubelet is the primary \u201cnode agent\u201d that runs on each node. It can register the node with the apiserver using one of: the hostname; a flag to override the hostname; or specific logic for a cloud provider.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":708,"question":"How can we redirect the output of one command to the another command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Place the commands connected with pipes (|).","answer_b":"Use the Xargs command","answer_c":"Use the stdin and stdout","answer_d":"Use the numbers 1 and 2 for standart input(stdin) and standart output(stdout)","answer_e":"Both commands which include stdin and stdout","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1081,"question":"Where are the online repositories configured on a Debian\/Ubuntu Machine","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/etc\/apt\/sources.list","answer_b":"\/etc\/apt\/yum.repos","answer_c":"\/etc\/fstab","answer_d":"\/etc\/apt\/repos","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":12,"question":"Which command is used to create an empty file.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mtfile","answer_b":"mkfile","answer_c":"file","answer_d":"touch","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":28,"question":"Where is Linux user list stored?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/etc\/users","answer_b":"\/usr\/local\/users","answer_c":"By running the command show users","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":223,"question":"Which keyword is used with the UPDATE command to change the value?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE","answer_b":"MODIFY","answer_c":"ADD","answer_d":"SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":742,"question":"How to dump pod logs, with label name=myLabel (stdout) in Kubernetes","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl log name=myLabel","answer_b":"kubectl pod -l name=myLabel","answer_c":"kubectl logs -l name=myLabel","answer_d":"kubectl logs -l .name[*]=myLabel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":13,"question":"What command, followed by the directory name is used to access that specific directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"cp","answer_b":"cd","answer_c":"access","answer_d":"acs","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":727,"question":"How to get a pod's YAML in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get pod my-pod --yaml","answer_b":"kubectl get pod my-pod -p yaml","answer_c":"kubectl get pod my-pod -f yaml","answer_d":"kubectl get pod my-pod -o yaml","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"}]